Well, the best the best advice for
fellow actors
is this. Know what your job is. About 18
years ago, I had this cognition that I
realized I was going into auditions
trying to get a job.
And that simply wasn't what I was doing.
It wasn't what I I'm supposed to be
doing. An actor is supposed to create a
compelling, interesting character that
serves the text. You present it in the
environment where your audition happens
and then you walk away and that's it.
Everything else is out of your control.
So don't even think of it. Don't focus
on that. You're not going there to get a
job. You're going there to present what
you do. You act and there it is and walk
away. And there's power in that. There's
confidence in that. And it's also saying
I can only do so much. And then the
decision of who might get a job is so
out of your control that it really when
you analyze it, it makes no sense to
hold on to that. That to me was a
breakthrough. And once I adapted that
philosophy,
I never looked back. And I've never been
busier in my life than once I grabbed
onto that and said, "The world